[
  {
    "id" : "1",
    "question" : "Who among Tom and Jerry usually succeed?",
    "answer" : [
      "Tom",
      "Jerry",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" :"Jerry",
  },
  {
    "id" : "2",
    "question" : "What was Jerry’s favorite food to eat?",
    "answer" : [
      "Cheese",
      "Cake",
      "Tom's Milk",
      "Steak"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Cheese",
  },
  {
    "id" : "3",
    "question" : " What is the color of Jerry?",
    "answer" : [
      "Red",
      "Brown",
      "Dark-Brown",
      "Light-Brown"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Brown",
  },
  {
    "id" : "4",
    "question" : "What Tom always do in the show?",
    "answer" : [
      "Chase Jerry",
      "Drinking milk",
      "Napping",
      "loving toodles"
     
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Chase Jerry",
  },
  {
    "id" : "5",
    "question" : "What is the color of Tom’s paws?",
    "answer" : [
      "Gray",
      "White",
      "Gray-white",
      "Dark-Gray"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "White",
  },
  {
    "id" : "6",
    "question" : "Who is Tom in the show?",
    "answer" : [
      "Cat",
      "Dog",
      "Mouse",
      "Duck"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Cat",
  },
  {
    "id" : "7",
    "question" : "What is the color of Tom’s fur on body?",
    "answer" : [
      "Gray-White",
      "Gray",
      "White",
      "Blue"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Gray-White",
  },
  {
    "id" : "8",
    "question" : "What is the name of the mouse?",
    "answer" : [
      "Tom",
      "Jerry",
      "Spike",
      "Tyke"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Jerry",
  },
  {
    "id" : "9",
    "question" : "Which animal was Spike?",
    "answer" : [
      "Cat",
      "Dog",
      "Mouse",
      "Duck"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Dog",
  },
  {
    "id" : "10",
    "question" : "What was Tom’s favorite food to eat?",
    "answer" : [
      "Milk",
      "Jerry",
      "Quacker",
      "Steak"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Milk",
  }
  
]
